It's a good thing no one saw us when we came in.
I’m sorry I had to lie to you.
I don’t care about that.
You know I know...
unless...
Can I ask you for one thing?
Don't tell my dad who you really are.
But I don't want to live a lie.
And do you not want to be with me?
Everything that happened. you feel the same way I do.
But it's wrong.
It's wrong because of our status,
our birth,
and because we are both women.
If we ignore all of that,
if we don't care who we are,
Would you still love me?
Yes.
I love you.
Then that's enough.
Can I hear you say you love me just one more time?
I love hearing the word "love" from your lips.
If that is what you want,
I will never stop.
What do you think it's like when someone is trapped in the darkness?
How do you feel?
I feel like I want to be touched by you.
I love the scent of jasmine on your body so much.
Especially right now.
This time, I won't be the only one enjoying this happiness.
Your clothes are completely soaked.
I might have to take them off for you.